afriwidescholarships.com 2018-12-04

# Privacy Policy -

Lokomo Simon Peter (" **Lokomo Simon Peter** ") operates afriwidescholarships.com and may operate other websites. It is Lokomo Simon Peter's policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites.

### Website Visitors

Like most website operators, Lokomo Simon Peter collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Lokomo Simon Peter's purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Lokomo Simon Peter's visitors use its website. From time to time, Lokomo Simon Peter may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

Lokomo Simon Peter also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments on afriwidescholarships.com blogs/sites. Lokomo Simon Peter only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below, except that commenter IP addresses and email addresses are visible and disclosed to the administrators of the blog/site where the comment was left.

### Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to Lokomo Simon Peter's websites choose to interact with Lokomo Simon Peter in ways that require Lokomo Simon Peter to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Lokomo Simon Peter gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up at [afriwidescholarships.com](http://www.afriwidescholarships.com/) to provide a username and email address. Those who engage in transactions with Lokomo Simon Peter are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, Lokomo Simon Peter collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor's interaction with Lokomo Simon Peter. Lokomo Simon Peter does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

### Aggregated Statistics

Lokomo Simon Peter may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. Lokomo Simon Peter may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, Lokomo Simon Peter does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

### Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

Lokomo Simon Peter discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Lokomo Simon Peter's behalf or to provide services available at Lokomo Simon Peter's websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Lokomo Simon Peter's websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Lokomo Simon Peter will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Lokomo Simon Peter discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when Lokomo Simon Peter believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Lokomo Simon Peter, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of an Lokomo Simon Peter website and have supplied your email address, Lokomo Simon Peter may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what's going on with Lokomo Simon Peter and our products. If you send us a request (for example via email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. Lokomo Simon Peter takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

### Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor's computer, and that the visitor's browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Lokomo Simon Peter uses cookies to help Lokomo Simon Peter identify and track visitors, their usage of Lokomo Simon Peter website, and their website access preferences. Lokomo Simon Peter visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Lokomo Simon Peter's websites, with the drawback that certain features of Lokomo Simon Peter's websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

### Business Transfers

If Lokomo Simon Peter, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, or in the unlikely event that Lokomo Simon Peter goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of Lokomo Simon Peter may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.

### Ads

Ads appearing on any of our websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by Lokomo Simon Peter and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

### Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, Lokomo Simon Peter may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Lokomo Simon Peter's sole discretion. Lokomo Simon Peter encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. If you have a afriwidescholarships.com account, you might also receive an alert informing you of these changes. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
